UNITE HERE Local 169 Files 6200/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE Local 169 Files
1938-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE
UNITE HERE Local 169
6200/001
5.33 cubic feet
5.3 linear ft.
Records.
Contains local union material regarding New School University security officers.
8255156
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 12, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; UNITE HERE (Organization); New School University
8255156
- Correspondence-Joanne Alicea (Payroll), 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Petition to Kerrey, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - NSU - Personnel -Farinella, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Murtha, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Letter to Muthra re: Fire Safety Director, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letter to Murtha re: Gentle, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Letter to Reed, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Greggory Spence, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Keila Tennent, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Absenteeism Info, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- New School Security Guards Articles, Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- New School Benefit Funds Merger, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NSU Differential 3-27-06, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- NSU Grievance and Petition re Holiday Pay, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NSU Check Info, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- High Rise Fire Safety Director, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- New School - New Hire Lists, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Supervisors Working Posts 12-6-05, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- NSU - Temporary Employees, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Dues/Benefits Problems - '04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Numerous Officers Back Dues and Benefits, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- NSU - Payroll Issues - Direct Deposit, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- New School Pay Problems, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Dues Checkoff Cards, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- New School University - Dues Cards Submitted to NSU, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- New School - Dues Increase 2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- NSU - Labor Mgt 12-8-05, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- New School Security Officers - Seniority List, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Labels - New School Officers (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Scope and Contents
  no date
- New School Shift Changes - Spring 2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- NSU - New Schedules - 11/19/04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- recent Problems in Schedules - 5/20/04 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- NSU - Tour Change Requests, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Roll Calls, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- NSU - Vacations, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- MSU - Vacation Checks, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- New School - Vacation Schedules, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Favoritism (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Stuck Lists, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Voluntary Lists, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Volunteer Lists, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- New School Weekly Schedules 10/5/04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- New School University - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- New School University - Security Officers' Manual, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- New School Security Advisories, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- New School - Security Advisors, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- New School - NYU Contract/SEIU Contract/Teamsters Contract, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- NSU Labor Management 12/2/04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- New School - Uniform Cleaning Services - Labor/Management 7-16-03, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- New School University - Meeting with Management, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- New School Schedules, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- New School Security Officers' Schedules, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- AAIS Split Second Security, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- New School - ESL/Communications, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- New School - Fire Safety Requirements, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- New School Insurance/Dues Checkoff Forms (Box 1, Folder 56)
- NSU - 403(b) - TIAA/CREF (Box 1, Folder 57)
- New School Meetings (Box 1, Folder 58)
- New School - Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- NSU Blended Rate Info, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 169 New School - CBA MOA 2003/6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- New School - Contract Negotiations - 7-17-03, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- New School Benefit Plans, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- New School University - Negotiations - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- New School University - Negotiations - 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NSU - Negotiations - 2003 - SEIU, NYU, Teamsters Contracts (Box 2, Folder 7)
- New School - Side Letters, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Temporary Employment Grievance, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Uniform Cleaning Write UPS and Problems, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NSU Contract Ratification 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Camera Stuff, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- COPE School - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Drug Free - Workplace - NSU, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Drug Testing Employee Assistance Program, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- New School Holiday Closing Policy, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Late Lunch Grievance, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Locker Room New School, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Late Lunch and Breaks, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- New School - Punch-in/Punch-out, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- post Problems, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- New School - Refusal of Overtime, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Responses to Dropped Grievance - Various Officers - To Be Filed, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Retro Pay - NSU, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Seniority - 55 E. 13th St. Post, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- NSU Steward Elections - 8/2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Stuck List Procedures (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Supervisors on Posts, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- New School University - Transit Strike Issue, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- New School - Unresponsive People Memo, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- NSU Vacation Selections - Summer 2004 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- New School Various, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- New School University - Workplace Violence, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Withdrawn NSU Grievances, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- New School University - Summary Plan Description, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- ALICO - HIPAA Awareness Information, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Hire/Fire Lists, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- New School Officers - Newsletters, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- New School - Pension Plan (Box 2, Folder 39)
- New School - Training Issues, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- New School Transit Strikes Policy, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- New School/ UAW Organizing, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- New School - Upgraded Security Precautions, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- New School Pension List 9/21/05, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Fire Safety Director 3-05, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- NSU - Drug Free Workplace Policy (Box 2, Folder 46)
- New School Contract Side Letters, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- New School grievance case: Suspension 5/2/05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- New School grievance, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- New School grievance case: Harassment, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Exhibit Part 1 Termination changed from suspension
- New School grievance case: Back Pay For Unused Time Off, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- New School grievance case: Unemployment Insurance, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Insubordination, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- New School grievance case: Certification, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- New School grievance case: Hours, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- New School grievance case 1/13/05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- New School grievance case: Return to Work, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- New School grievance case: Health Issue - 2/06, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- New School grievance case: Suspension/EAP, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- New School grievance case: Promotion, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- New School grievance case: Poor Job Performance 2-28-05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- New School grievance case: Medical Condition, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Not Grieved, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- New School grievance case: Off Post 4/6/05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- New School grievance case: Extension of Probation, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- New School grievance case: Promotion, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- New School grievance case: Out of Uniform and unnecessary Conversations, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Absenteeism, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Insubordination, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- New School grievance case: 9/9/03 - Refusal to Work O.T., 2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Out of Uniform, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- New School grievance case: Suspension Rescinded, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- New School grievance case: Harassment, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- New School grievance case: Unemployment Settlement, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- New School grievance case: COBRA Application, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- New School grievance case: Leave of Absence 2/6/06, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Absenteeism, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- New School grievance case: Vacation Accrual, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- New School grievance case: Absences 2/4/05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- New School grievance case: Suspension/FMLA 4-6-05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- New School grievance case: Unexcused Absences, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- New School grievance case: Harassment, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- New School grievance case: Late Coming from Lunch, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- New School grievance case: Rafael Vera, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- New School grievance case: Settlement, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- New School grievance case: Meals, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- New School grievance case: Reading Paper at Post, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- New School grievance case: Suspension 4/11/05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- New School grievance case: Injury, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- New School grievance case, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- New School grievance case: Sick Day, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- New School grievance case: Harassment, Suspension, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- New School grievance case: Suspension 9-16-05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- New School grievance case: Termination - Absenteeism, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- New School grievance case: Unemployment, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Refusal of O.T., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- New School grievance case: Complaint Against Another Person - 1-12-06, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- New School grievance case: Personal Day, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- New School grievance case: Suspension, Sleeping, 2003-2006 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- New School grievance case: Alcohol on Breath 3 Day Suspension, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- New School grievance case: Sleeping 11/28/05 One Day Suspension - not Grieved, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- New School grievance case: Withdrawal of Post Grievance, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- New School grievance case: Suspension, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Absenteeism, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- New School grievance case: Unauthorized Phone Call 3-10-05, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- New School grievance case: Call-In, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- New School grievance case: AWOL Warning, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- New School grievance case: Settlement 11-3-05 Alcohol on Breath, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- New School grievance case, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- New School grievance case, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- New School grievance case: Vacation/Workers Comp Claim, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Nov 5, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- New School grievance case, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- New School grievance case: Denial of Leave of Absence, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- New School grievance case: Refusal to Accept Packages, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- New School grievance case: Mohammed Kalaz, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- New School grievance case: Suspension 11/28/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- New School grievance case: Failure to Notify Reed, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- New School grievance case: Pre-Discipline 1) No Hat 2) Failure to Notify Reed, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- New School grievance case: Lost Radio, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- New School grievance case: Medical, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- New School grievance case: Pension 718-467-4417, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- New School grievance case: Suspension 7/27/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- New School grievance case: Termination - Drug Test Failure, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Lateness, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- New School grievance case: Weekends, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- New School grievance case: Harassment, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- New School grievance case: Unnecessary Conversations, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- New School grievance case: Late Lunches, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- New School grievance case: Termination 1/13/06, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- New School grievance case: Class Action Differential, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- New School grievance case: Disability, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- New School grievance case: Pay - 7/27/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- New School grievance case: Suspension, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- New School grievance case, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- New School grievance case: Days Off 10-17-01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- New School grievance case: Holiday Call-In, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- New School grievance case: Lateness 1/28/02, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- New School grievance case: Job Abandonment, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 98)
- New School grievance case: Lost Days Grievance 10-17-01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Recognition Agreement, Disclaimer & Contract Extension Agreement, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 100)
- New School grievance case: Statement re: Loeb Hall Incident, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  no grievance filed
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- New School grievance case: Shift Change, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- New School grievance case: Dues Deductions/Healthcare Payments, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  step 1:
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New School grievance case: Insubordination, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  1st Step to management 11/13
- New School grievance case: Readng on Job (Box 4, Folder 7)
  empty folder- no date
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- New School grievance case: 560 7th Post, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- New School grievance case: Promotion, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- New School grievance case: Health Benefit Payment, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New School grievance case: Insurance - Problems, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- New School grievance case, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- New School grievance case: Sleeping 1 Day Suspension 9-26-05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- New School grievance case: Unsatisfactory Job Performance 11/30/05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Lateness 9/6/05 - Warning Not Grieved, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- New School grievance case: Job Abandonment, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- New School grievance case: Sleeping on Job, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- New School grievance case: Statement re Camera Adjustment, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- New School grievance case, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Lateness 6-20-05 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- New School grievance case: Tour Change Request, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- New School grievance case: AWOL 2-21-05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- New School grievance case: Unexcused Absence 3-10-05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Absenteeism, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- New School grievance case: Suspension Refusing Overtime, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- New School grievance case: Suspension Mocking Lasalle, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- New School grievance case: Level IV Promotion Request, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- New School grievance case: Pay Issue 4/13/06, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- New School grievance case: Late from Lunch, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- New School grievance case: Workers Comp, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- New School grievance case: Reading on Duty 4/6/05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- New School grievance case: Workers Comp, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- New School grievance case: Letter to Move to Level D, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- New School grievance case: Suspension 12/12/01, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- New School grievance case: New School Personal (Box 4, Folder 38)
- New School grievance case: Promotion to Level II, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- New School grievance case: Incident at 65 5th Ave, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- New School grievance case: Compliant 1/12/04, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- New School grievance case: Inappropriate Behavior 0 Refer to EAP 10-17-05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- New School grievance case: Suspension Refusing to do Overtime, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- New School grievance case: Theft of Time, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- New School grievance case: Discriminatory Harassment, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- New School grievance case: Unsatisfactory Job Performance, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Settled 10-28-03
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- New School grievance case: Reading on Duty 4/8/05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- New School grievance case: Prescription Problem, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- New School grievance case: Denial of Overtime, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  Step 3 - 8/18 filing for failure to communicate (memo); (I can't read the remainder written-mh)
- New School grievance case: Denial of O.T. (Post Assignments), 2004 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Step 3-8-18
- New School grievance case: Direct Deposit Grievance, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- New School grievance case: Lateness 11/14/05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- New School grievance case: Changing Posts, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- New School grievance case: Day Off Requests, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- New School grievance case: Warning - Off Post, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- New School grievance case: Lateness from Break, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- New School grievance case: Warning Notice, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- New School grievance case: Forced Overtime, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- New School grievance case: Pay, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- New School grievance case: Arbitration Settlement, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- New School grievance case: Unnecessary Conversations, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  1st Step Hearing 11-13, Response 11-13
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- New School grievance case: Overpay, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- New School grievance case: Termination - Drinking on the Job, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- New School grievance case: Senior Security Promotion, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- New School grievance case: Off Post Warning, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- New School grievance case: Suspension Personal Day, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- New School grievance case: Statement, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- New School grievance case: Medical NSU, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- New School grievance case: Pension Calculation, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- New School grievance case: Direct Deposit Problem 12-04, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- New School grievance case: Medical Problems/Disability, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- New School grievance case: LOA - 10/16/04, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- New School grievance case: Scheduling and O.T., 2003 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- New School grievance case: Retirement, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- New School grievance case: Medicaid/Medicare, 1985-1990 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- New School grievance case: FMLA, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- New School grievance case: Unexcused Absences, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  Dr. Khaleeg Arshed 718-729-8794; 718-426-8717
- New School grievance case: Personal Day, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- New School grievance case: Asleep, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- New School grievance case, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- New School grievance case: Failure to Follow Instructions, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- New School grievance case: Out of Uniform, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- New School grievance case, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- New School grievance case: Lateness from Break, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- New School grievance case: Call Out Warning, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- New School grievance case: Sleeping on Duty, Suspension, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Lateness, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 90)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Absences, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- New School grievance case: Warning Notice, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- New School grievance case: Termination Lateness, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 94)
- New School grievance case: Unexpected Absences 3-10-05 (7/7/05-2nd), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 95)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Lateness 6/13/04, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 96)
- New School grievance case: Expired License, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 97)
- New School grievance case: 3 Day Suspension - Sleeping on Duty, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 98)
- New School grievance case: Chronic Lateness, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 99)
- New School grievance case: Personal/Sick Days, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 100)
- New School grievance case: Lateness, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  1st Step fired 11-13
- New School grievance case: Reading on Duty 4/6/05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 102)
- New School grievance case: Denial Of Overtime, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 103)
- New School grievance case: Complaint Against Walsh, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 104)
- New School grievance case: Unexpected Absences - Warning, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 105)
- New School grievance case: Off Post - 1st and Second Warnings, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- New School grievance case: Level 3 Qualifications, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 107)
- New School grievance case: Disability, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 108)
- New School grievance case: Termination, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 109)
- New School grievance case: Post Abandonment 2 Day Suspension, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 110)
- New School grievance case, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 111)
- New School grievance case: Suspension Off Post 0 Not Grieved 10-7-05, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 112)
- New School grievance case: Disability, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 113)
- New School grievance case: Unexcused Absences - 12/2/04, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 114)
- New School grievance case: Absenteeism, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 115)
- New School grievance case: Sick, Vacation Accruals, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 116)
- New School grievance case: Suspension - Refusal of O.T., 2004 (Box 4, Folder 117)
- New School grievance case: Termination Fraudulent Information, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 118)
- New School grievance case: Sleeping, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 119)
- New School grievance case: Sleeping on Duty, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 120)
- New School grievance case: Shift Change, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 121)
- New School grievance case: Weekend Request, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 122)
- New School grievance case: RDO Change Request, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 123)
- New School grievance case: Change in Days Off, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 124)